<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Philosophy on Sir Abdisalam | The Website</title>
    <link>http://localhost:56459/tags/philosophy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Philosophy on Sir Abdisalam | The Website</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 00:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:56459/tags/philosophy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Desire and Its Nature Pt 3 : Discipline</title>
      <link>http://localhost:56459/blog/desire-pt3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:56459/blog/desire-pt3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style=&#34;text-align: center; font-style: italic; margin: 30px 0;&#34;&gt;&#xA;&#34;The soul in its early stages is like a rebellious horse. If not trained, it will never obey you.&#34;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;— Ibn Qayyim al-Jawziyya&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I think the more I reflect on this series, the more I realize how little I actually knew about desire when I first started writing it all. It seemed like something simple at the start. A feeling really only. Something that could either be ignored or acted on. But now, after sitting with it, questioning , &lt;i&gt;if i really wanted this&lt;/i&gt;, falling to it sometimes and trying to rise again. The act of wanting, and that of wanting new things, which I mentioned in the last part, is what desire is—if not controlled with discipline, NOT pure motivation.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Desire and Its Nature – Pt. 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:56459/blog/desire-nature-pt2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:56459/blog/desire-nature-pt2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style=&#34;text-align: center; font-style: italic; margin: 30px 0;&#34;&gt;&#xA;&#34;Man is broad, too broad. I&#39;d have him narrower.&#34;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;— Fyodor Dostoevsky&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is a continuation of my earlier thoughts on desire. I still don’t have clear answers, but I am starting to see the layers more clearly. The surface is really obvious. Beneath it, things get harder and harder to define.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What I’ve been noticing lately is how quickly desire changes. The moment one goes out, another takes its place. It is not about what is wanted, but about the state of wanting itself (&lt;i&gt; which I think is insane to think of&lt;/i&gt; ). That condition seems to persist, regardless of whether anything is actually missing at all.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Desire and it&#39;s Nature</title>
      <link>http://localhost:56459/blog/desire-evil/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:56459/blog/desire-evil/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style=&#34;text-align: center; font-style: italic; margin: 30px 0;&#34;&gt;&#xA;&#34;The chains of habit are too weak to be felt until they are too strong to be broken.&#34;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;— Samuel Johnson&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Recently, I have been thinking if my desires-good or bad-control me? Desire. It really is one of the greatest walls standing between a man and his own peace. Not all desires are evil, but the moment they become the master, the soul begins to rot. I have come to see more recently, there is something deceptive about it, the way it starts as a whisper—gentle, almost harmless. A itching for ease, for pleasure, for something just out of reach. It does not force itself upon you; it only asks. Wouldn&amp;rsquo;t it be easier? Wouldn&amp;rsquo;t it be nice? What harm is there in just this once? Or What if I just&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
