<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Sir Abdisalam on Sir Abdisalam | The Website</title><link>https://www.abdisalam.blog/tags/sir-abdisalam/</link><description>Recent content in Sir Abdisalam on Sir Abdisalam | The Website</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2024 11:43:53 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.abdisalam.blog/tags/sir-abdisalam/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>2024 Reflection</title><link>https://www.abdisalam.blog/blog/reflection/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2024 11:43:53 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://www.abdisalam.blog/blog/reflection/</guid><description>&lt;p>2024 . What a year it was. The start of the year was epic, I had so much motivation to go do it all but as the year went by that motivation went away slowly. Which is why the quote&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>&amp;ldquo;Thinking is easy, acting is difficult, and to put one’s thoughts into action is the most difficult thing in the world.&amp;rdquo; &amp;ndash; Johann Wolfgang von Goethe&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;p>Really hits the head now, looking back throughout the year. I found myself casually flying through specific months, and that specific motivation I once had in January seemed more of a ghost of my thoughts. It really is easy to THINK, but to DO—this is truly what isn’t easy. But I must give myself credit; this year, I have taken lessons and wrote them down in my core memory. Also what is a year without lesson ay?&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>About Me</title><link>https://www.abdisalam.blog/about/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 20:58:06 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://www.abdisalam.blog/about/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="abdisalam-sharif-ali">Abdisalam Sharif Ali&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://www.abdisalam.blog/images/cam.png" alt="abdi">&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>Well&amp;hellip; Welcome!
I&amp;rsquo;m a lover of books-classical ones mostly-a runner at heart, and someone who&amp;rsquo;s never shy about speaking my mind. If there&amp;rsquo;s one thing you should know about me, it&amp;rsquo;s that I believe in standing up for what I think is right-and doing something about it.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I am in love with trying to bring education everywhere (pretty crazy that isn&amp;rsquo;t the case). I&amp;rsquo;m also a huge fan of the journalism industry and believe that traditional journalism is dying at the expense of money and greed (but I&amp;rsquo;ll probably go on and on about this in a blog post later).&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>